<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <!-- Llama query template -->
    <string name="object_query_template">
        Briefly describe the {{object_name}} in this image. Specifically, provide technical details or information about its construction, but do not guess details which are not apparent in the photo.
    </string>

    <!-- Camera status -->
    <string name="camera_status_off">Paused</string>
    <string name="camera_status_on">Scanning</string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="btn_got_it">Got It</string>
    <string name="btn_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="btn_dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="btn_generate_objects">Generate Objects</string>

    <!-- Content descriptions -->
    <string name="camera_controls_button_description">Play/pause button</string>
    <string name="help_button_description">Help button</string>
    <string name="refrigerator_image_description">Refrigerator</string>
    <string name="dot">Dot</string>

    <!-- Welcome panel -->
    <string name="notice">
        This application uses generative AI to describe the content of images, and those responses may be inaccurate or inappropriate. [Learn More](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/guide/genai/). Your queries and the generative AI responses are not retained by Meta.
    </string>
    <string name="camera_controls_title">Camera Controls</string>
    <string name="camera_controls_1">
        Look at your left palm to activate camera scanner controls.
    </string>
    <string name="camera_controls_2">
        Press play to begin the scan, and pause to end scanning.
    </string>

    <!-- Tips -->
    <string name="select_object_title">Select Object</string>
    <string
    name="select_object_copy"
  >Select an object to learn more information about it.</string>
    <string name="no_objects_detected_title">No Objects Detected</string>
    <string
    name="no_objects_detected_body"
  >Try moving to a different room or location, or select one of the generated objects.</string>
    <string name="find_objects_title">Find Curated Objects</string>
    <string
    name="find_objects_body"
  >Look for one of the curated objects: a phone, fridge, or television. Or select one of the generated objects.</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_body">
        You can scan your surroundings to identify objects with the play button. Select a detected object to learn more about it, or choose from generated objects.
    </string>

    <!-- Curated objects copy -->
    <string name="fridge_body_copy">
        ## More Room. More Organization. More Fun!\n\n
        - Stay Connected: Share photos, stream music or video, read recipes, and more all from your fridge\'s AI companion.\n
        - Chill Out: Cool your summertime drink with fresh cubed or crushed ice with the Dual Auto Ice Maker.\n
        - Better Workflow: A flat-front fridge design with a recessed drawer handle blends into any kitchen beautifully.
    </string>
    <string name="tv_body_copy">
        ## Unmatched Quality, Endless Watchability.\n\n
        - Stunning Views: With 4k resolution, enhanced picture quality and 100% color volume, you\'ve never seen your content like this before.\n
        - Smartly Secure: Connect your accounts worry-free with a top-of-the-line security system, keeping your data locked tight and your viewing hassle-free.\n
        - All Content, All the Time: Connect your streaming apps, or search our library of 5000+ free titles. Never miss a title again!
    </string>
    <string name="phone_body_copy">
        ## Experience More. Do More. Effortlessly.\n\n
        - Never Stop Playing: With up to 36 hours of video playback, you\'re good to go all day on a single charge.\n
        - Capture the Moment: With an unmatched 2-in-1 camera system, you\'ll get the shot you want no matter the lighting.\n
        - Powerfully Professional: 6-core GPU, 6 core CPU, and a neural engine mean you\'ve never been faster at getting things done.
    </string>
</resources>
